<resources>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="app_name">HIMMAT</string>
    <string name="guidelines_header">
        DAILY SCHEDULE FOR HOME ISOLATION FOR MILD COVID PATIENTS\n
        (NOT A SUBSTITUTE FOR DOCTOR’S ADVICE)
    </string>

    <string name="guidelines_head_1">1. 7AM to 9AM</string>

    <string name="guidelines_1">
        \nCheck temperature\n
        \nCheck Oxygen SpO2 saturation levels using an oxymeter (if below 94%, consult a doctor)\n
        \nTake one tablet of Pantoprazole 40mg\n
        \n(any brand for example Pan) with water\n
        \nGargle with Chlorhexidine or salt water\n
    </string>

    <string name="guidelines_head_2">2. 9AM to 11AM</string>

    <string name="guidelines_2">
        \nSteam inhalation (preferably with the green capsule, any brand)\n
        \nGargle with Chlorhexidine or salt water.\n
        \n(Only if recommended by a doctor) Azithromycin 500mg.\n
        \nVitamin ‘C’ tablet (any brand, Limcee is one of them).\n
        \nZinc and Multi-vitamin tablets (any brand, Zincovit is one of them)\n
        \nParacetamol (if fever or aches, available in many brands e.g. Dolo, Calpol, Crocin, Paracip)\n
        \nAny other medicine recommended post breakfast by the doctor.\n
        \nTake a fruit (coconut water cheekoo/sapota, apple, any fruit that you like)\n
    </string>


    <string name="guidelines_head_3">3. 11AM to 01PM</string>

    <string name="guidelines_3">
        \nCheck temperature\n
        \nTake the 6 minutes walk test (walk for 6 minutes normally, check oxygen SpO2 saturation levels before and after the walk (if below 94%, consult a doctor immediately). If you can’t do the 6 minutes walk, check oxygen normally.\n
        \nLunch\n
        \nVitamin ‘D3’ (any brand, for example- Uprise) ONLY ONCE A WEEK. Not more than ONCE A WEEK.\n
        \n Any other medicine post lunch advised by doctor.\n
    </string>


    <string name="guidelines_head_4">4. 01PM to 4PM</string>

    <string name="guidelines_4">
        \nRest adequately\n
        \nSteam inhalation (preferably with the green capsule, any brand)\n
        \nDrink Karha/Kahwa (Kashmiri Tea)/ any warm beverage if Kahwa not available.\n
        \nVitamin ‘C’ tablet (any brand, Limcee is one of them)\n
    </string>


    <string name="guidelines_head_5">5. 4PM to 6PM</string>

    <string name="guidelines_5">
        \nCheck Temperature.\n
        \nCheck Oxygen SpO2 saturation levels using an oxymeter (If below 94% consult a doctor immediately).\n
        \nDrink coconut water.\n
        \nVitamin ‘C’ tablet (any brand, Limcee is one of them).\n
        \nParacetamol (If fever or aches, available in many brands e.g. Dolo, Calpol, Crocin, Paracip)\n
    </string>


    <string name="guidelines_head_6">6. 6PM to 7PM</string>

    <string name="guidelines_6">
        \nSteam inhalation (preferably with the green capsule, any brand).\n
        \nGargle with chlorhexidine or salt water.\n
        \nHave a soup.\n
    </string>

    <string name="guidelines_head_7">7. 7PM to 9PM</string>

    <string name="guidelines_7">
        \nCheck temperature\n
        \nCheck oxygen SpO2 saturation levels using an oxymeter (If below 94% consult a doctor immediately)\n
        \nDinner\n
        \nParacetamol (if fever or aches, available in many brands e.g. Dolo, Calpol, Crocin, Paracip)\n
    </string>

    <string name="guidelines_head_8">8. 9PM to Bedtime</string>

    <string name="guidelines_8">
        \nCheck temperature.\n
        \nCheck oxygen SpO2 saturation levels using an oxymeter (if below 94% consult a doctor immediately)\n
        \nSteam inhalation (preferably with the green capsule, any brand)\n
        \nAny warm drink (Milk with Haldi (turmeric) or karha (kadha) or hot water)\n
        \nCongratulate yourself on following this routine.\n
        \nWrite a diary, speak with friends, listen to music, make a vacation plan for the next 2 year - do anything else you like to do\n
        \nBe grateful and sleep with a positive attitude.\n
    </string>

    <string name="terms_conditions"><![CDATA[Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <string name="no_data_found">No Data found</string>
</resources>